search-results.com 2017-06-06

# Search-results.com Privacy

| 

## Privacy Policy for Search-Results.com

_Effective date: June 4, 2015_

Search-Results.com is a website owned and operated by APN, LLC (” APN ” or ” we ”), a wholly owned business of IAC, which operates several dozen brands. For a list of all of IAC's businesses, please visit [www.iac.com](http://www.iac.com/).

At Search-Results.com, we respect your privacy, and we understand the importance of the information you entrust to us. We provide this Privacy Policy so that our users ("you") will know what information is being collected about you and your activities on Search-Results.com, how that information is being used, and with whom it is being shared. This Privacy Policy describes the online privacy practices applicable to the web pages within the Internet domain Search-Results.com including all subdomains thereunder and specifically including any subdomain optimized for use on mobile devices ( “ **Search-Results** ” or the “ **Site** ”) and the various services (“ **Site Services** ”) we provide on or through the Site. 

By using the Site and Services you consent to our collection and use of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. As our privacy practices evolve, we will update this privacy policy. Any material changes in our privacy practices will be posted prominently on this page.   
If you are accessing the Site from a mobile device (e.g. a ” smartphone ”) through the operation of an APN or third party application downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile application may provide you such access by placing a search icon on your home screen. In order to remove the search icon on the homepage of your mobile device, click and hold the search icon, and depending on the make and model of your mobile device, either (i) drag it to the trash in the bottom of the screen, (ii) click the red "x" bottom on the top right corner of the search icon, or (iii) remove the search icon as you would remove any icon in the normal and customary manner effectuated through your mobile device.   
If you have any questions about our privacy practices, you can contact us via email by clicking [here](mailto:privacy@MySearch.com). You can also write to our Privacy Officer at: 

APN, LLC   
Attention: Legal Department   
555 West 18th Street   
New York, NY, 10011   

What types of information do we collect when you use the Site and Site Services?

How may we use the information we collect?

How are cookies used on the Site?

What information may we share with third parties?

What happens when you leave the Site to go to other Internet sites?

What is our policy regarding personally identifiable information from children under 13?

Do we take security precautions to protect your information?

Are there special considerations if you are visiting the Site from outside of the United States?

### What types of information do we collect when you use the Site and Site Services?

Each time you visit the Site, we collect the limited information that your browser makes available. This information includes: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type; (d) your browser language; and (e) the data in any undeleted "cookies" that your browser previously accepted from us (see "How are cookies used on the Site?" below). Additionally, when you enter a search query using the Site or Services, we will receive the query text and process it, together with the above data, to return a search results page to you. If you have modified your browser settings so that address-bar search queries and erroneous domain name system (DNS) requests are submitted to us, we may also receive any search query or misspelled URL that you enter into your browser's address bar. 

If you access the Site through a mobile device we may collect additional information including: (i) the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your mobile device; (ii) one way hashed device ID; (iii) your mobile device language; (iv) your mobile device OS (operating system); (v) your mobile device make and model; (vi) a new session on the Site; (v) the duration you spend on the Site; (vi) your clicks on ads or links in connection with the Site.

Some of the foregoing information may be collected via a third party (e.g., comScore) pixel or web beacon and/or information stored in cookies. We do not link the information we store in these cookies to any personally identifiable information.

The Site and Site Services usually do not require registration or submission of an account name or email address in order to use them. However, we will collect your email address if you submit a help request to us via email. The amount of information that you choose to disclose to us is completely up to you.

### How may we use the information we collect?

We use the information that we collect to facilitate the delivery of relevant and/or targeted search results, improve the overall quality of your experience with the Site and Site Services, and to facilitate evaluation, improvement, and development of the Site Services. We aggregate query information for internal reporting purposes and optimization of advertising revenue. We count, track, and aggregate our visitors' activities in our analysis of general traffic flows at the Site (e.g., tracking where users come from, what pages they select within the Site, how they interact with search results, etc.). 

Information about the search queries you submit to the Sites and how you interact with search results may also be used to personalize the content and advertisements that we present to you. We may, based on the search queries you submit and the search results you select (including paid search results), draw inferences about your interests and display advertisements matched to such interests. You may receive such customized ads on the Site and on third-party sites (see also "What information do we share with third parties?" below). If you would like to terminate and Search-results's access to your search history you may remove our cookies from your computer (see "How are cookies used on the Sites?" below and consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies).

If you choose to submit your name, email address, or other information, we may use such information to contact you to respond to a request from you, or in connection with legal proceedings, or if there has been a violation of our Terms of Service  or this Privacy Policy. We do not associate your search queries or selected search results in any manner with your name, email address, or other information, unless required to do so by legal process.

### How are cookies used on the Sites?

We use cookies and other technology such as pixel tags to track traffic flow and patterns of travel within and among the Site. Cookies are a standard Internet technology that allows us to store and retrieve information on a user's system. To understand more about cookies click here. Our web server automatically asks a new user's browser whether it will accept our cookie file. If the user's browser accepts our cookie, our web server will record the cookie's unique ID for our use in internal reporting and for customized advertising (see "How may we use the information that we collect?" above). Some or all of your search queries and interactions with search results on the Site is associated with your unique cookie ID. When you use the Site we may use your cookie data to customize the Services and advertisements delivered to you (see "Data collection and sharing involving third parties" below). 

If you would like to remove our cookies from your computer, you can delete them using your browser (consult your browser's "help" menu to learn how to delete cookies). If you would like to remove our cookies from your mobile device, you should consult your mobile device privacy and the browser tabs in the "Settings" menu to learn how to change the settings on your mobile device and clear cookies. If you choose to decline or remove cookies, please note that this may affect the quality of the Site Services.

We do not use cookies to track your use of the Internet in any other way, or associate your name, email address, or personal information with your cookie data. We do not disclose cookie information to third parties, except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy (see "What information do we share with third parties?" below). 

_Use of cookies on our Site by third parties_. We use third-party companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to the Site in order to present advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements on the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with the Site. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad-serving company might collect from you. These companies have their own recordkeeping and data-retention policies. If you would like to consider your options for limiting use of such information by advertising companies, or would like to learn more about this practice, please click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. We also use third party vendors to help us better understand our user demographics. These vendors may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as pixel tags in connection with the Site to provide their services to us. 

### What information may we share with third parties?

We do not share your name name, or email address or any other personal information with third parties for the purpose of enabling them to send you information about their products or services (or for any other purpose, except to respond to legal process as described below). 

_Third-party service providers_.Some elements or features of the Site, such as the sponsored results advertising on our Site pages, are supplied to us by one or more third parties under contract.Some elements or features of the Site, such as the sponsored results advertising on our Site pages, are supplied to us by one or more third parties under contract. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that third-party service providers might collect from you. These companies have their own recordkeeping and data-retention policies. If you would like to consider your options for limiting use of such information by advertising companies, or would like to learn more about this practice, please click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>. You may also choose to not participate in Microsoft personalized advertising services, if applicable, by following the instructions here: <https://choice.microsoft.com/en-US>.

We may supply some of the information we collect from you to those third parties so that they can provide those elements or features for display on the Site. Some of the information you input may be supplied directly to our service providers so they can provide some of the services and features in connection with our Site. In addition, we may share the following information with third parties: (a) your Internet Protocol (IP) address; (b) the address of the last URL you visited before clicking through to the Site; (c) your browser and platform type; (d) your browser language; (e) the data in any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us; (f) the search queries you submit; and/or (g) other information described in the "What types of information do we collect when you use the Site and Site Services" section of this policy above. For example, when you submit a query, we transmit it (and some of the related information described above) to our paid-listing providers in order to generate relevant advertising to display in response to your query and to optimize the number and quality of sponsored results that will be provided to you on the Site. We may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers. If you provide us with answers to voluntary survey questions, we may furnish this information to our advertisers and partners in the form of group statistics compiled from our users' answers to such questions.

_Search Partners_. If you have accessed the Site through an APN or third party application installed on your computer or mobile device, then our search partners that developed or distributed the search application may collect information about you including the queries you submit via our Site, the search application or your browser, as well as the search results and ads you click on and the address of the web pages you previously listed. 

We have agreements in place with our search partners and our third-party service providers that limits their use and disclosure of any information about you that you provide directly to us (i.e., information not provided directly by you to the applicable search partner or third-party service providers.

Law enforcement/legal requirements. We may disclose any information you voluntarily submit to us, as well as any other information we have about you (such as your IP address, the search queries you have submitted, and the search results you have selected) in order to comply with court orders, subpoenas, or regulatory obligations, or when otherwise required to do so by law. We also may disclose such information in compliance with a law-enforcement or other governmental request, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our Terms of Service. 

_Corporate restructuring_. We also may transfer your information to a third party if we or any of our affiliates are involved in a corporate restructuring (e.g., a sale, merger, or other transfer of assets).

### What happens when you leave the Site to go to other Internet sites?

We do not control the information collection and dissemination policies of third-party companies. When you are on the Site, you may be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, if you click on a search result, the click may take you to a third-party website. These other sites may independently collect data from or about you, solicit information from you, or place their own cookies on your computer. We are not responsible for any use of the information such third-party sites may collect. 

We also offer you access to “ co-branded “ services that are jointly provided by us and selected companies. In many cases, these co-branded services will contain the Site branding, but might not be hosted by us. You may notice that you are on a co-branded site if the pages say “ provided by Search-Results “ and/or if our standard branding is otherwise displayed on the page. In such cases, you should click on the privacy link on the page to determine which company's privacy policy applies to the information you enter on the page. Even if the page is governed by a separate privacy policy, we might be entitled to receive information about you when using that service. If you elect to provide registration information when using a co-branded service, the information you provide may be shared and/or retained by the provider of that service in accordance with its own privacy policy and terms of service. 

We encourage you to consult the privacy policies of such other companies and to contact them directly if you have any questions about their use of your information. 

### What is our policy regarding personally identifiable information from children under 13?

We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we determine that a user is under 13, we will immediately delete all information pertaining to that user. 

### Do we take security precautions to protect your information?

We have security measures in place that are designed to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to information we collect online. We utilize both industry and proprietary standards to preserve the confidentiality of information. We seek to limit access to our users' information to employees who we believe reasonably need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to perform their jobs. These employees have been informed of the need to maintain the security and confidentiality of such information. Unfortunately, no security system can be 100% secure; accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that we collect online.

### Are there special considerations if you are visiting the Site from outside of the United States?

If you are visiting the Site from outside of the United States, your information will be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data-protection and other laws in the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your own country. Please be assured, however, that we seek to take reasonable steps to protect your privacy. By using the Site Services, you consent to the transfer of your information to our facilities and those third parties with whom we may share it as described in this Privacy Policy.
